Leonard Everett Fisher Papers
© 2010 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Exhibits: Programs, Correspondence / Appearance programs, 1946-1999
  - Speeches/Eulogies
    - University of Southern Mississippi, medallion speech, 1979 March 1 (Box 100:273)
    - Westport Library, speech, 1980 September 16 (Box 100:274)
    - "Creative Rights and American Destiny, 1981 November 21 (Box 101:275)
    - "The Jewish Connection", 1981 December 4 (Box 101:276)
    - National Jewish Book Council (?), 1981 May 3 (Box 101:277)
    - Children's Book Guild, 1st and 2nd drafts, 1989 November 18 (Box 101:278)
    - Children's Book Guild, 1989 November (Box 101:279)
    - "History for Young and Old..." 1st draft, 1990 November 1 (Box 101:280)
    - "History for Young and Old..." 2nd draft, 1990 November 2 (Box 101:281)
    - Catholic Library Association convention, Regina medal, 1991 April 2 (Box 101:282)
    - "Censorship and the Arts" IRA 38th Convention, 1993 April 28 (Box 101:283)
    - "Children's Books a Different Discipline", 1993 November 11 (Box 101:284)
    - "Mythology in Children's Books", Society of illustrators, 1993 November 11 (Box 101:285)
    - "Using Trade Books Across the Curriculum", 1994 May 12 (Box 101:286)
    - "Imaginings and Images", May Hill Arbuthnot Lectureship, 1995 May 5 (Box 101:287)
    - "Imaginings and Images", May Hill Arbuthnot Lectureship, 1995 May 5 (Box 101:288)
    - "The More Things Change..." ALA, 1995 June 23 (Box 101:289)
    - "The More Things Change..." ALA, 1995 June 23 (Box 101:290)
    - "Change is Good", Eastern MA Library Association, 1996 January 11 (Box 101:291)
    - "From Xenophon to Gutenberg", 1996 April 30 (Box 101:292)
    - Graduation speech given at Paier, 1998 June 7 (Box 101:293)
    - Festivals, 1996 (Box 102:311)
    - Galileo, 1992 (Box 102:312)
    - Gandhi, 1995 (Box 102:313)
    - The Glassblowers Children, 1973 (Box 102:314)
    - Gods and Goddesses of Ancient Egypt, 1997 (Box 102:315A)
    - The Great Wall of China, 1986 (Box 102:315)
    - Gutenberg, 1993 (Box 102:316)
    - If You Ever Meet A Whale, 1992 (Box 102:317)
    - Jason and the Golden Fleece, 1990 (Box 102:318)
    - The Jetty Chronicles, 1998+ (Box 102:319A)
    - Journey of the Gray Whales, 1974 (Box 102:319)
    - Kinderdike, 1993 (Box 102:320)
    - Letters From Italy, 1977 (Box 102:321)
    - The Liberty Book, 1976 (Box 102:322)
    - Little Frog's Song, 1991 (Box 102:323)
    - Look Around!, 1987 (Box 102:324)
    - Lora, Lorita, 1969 (Box 102:325)
    - The Luck of Roaring Camp & Three Other Stories, 1968-1969 (Box 102:326)
    - Malachy's Gold, 1968 (Box 102:327)
    - Marie Curie, 1994 (Box 102:328)
    - Monticello, 1988 (Box 102:329)
    - Moses, 1996 (Box 102:330)
    - Niagara Falls, 1996 (Box 102:331)
    - The Night Country, 1971 (Box 102:332)
    - Nineteenth Century America Series, 1979 (Box 103:333)
    - Noonan, 1984 (Box 103:334)
    - Number Art, 1983 (Box 103:335)
    - The Olympians, 1984 (Box 103:336)
    - The Oregon Trail, 1991 (Box 103:337)
    - Picture Book of Revolutionary War Heroes, 1870 (Box 103:338)
    - Prince Henry the Navigator, 1990 (Box 103:339)
    - Pyramid of the Sun, Pyramid of the Moon, 1988 (Box 103:340)
    - Rip Van Winkle, 1968 (Box 103:341)
  - Reviews of Books
    - ABC Exhibit, 1991 (Box 102:294)
    - Across the Sea From Galway, 1975 (Box 102:295)
    - The Alamo, 1987 (Box 102:296)
    - All Times All Peoples, 1980 (Box 102:297)
    - Alphabet Art & Number Art, 1979-1983 (Box 102:298)
    - Anasazi, 1998+ (Box 102:299A)
    - The Art Experience, 1973 (Box 102:299)
    - The Blacksmiths, 1975 (Box 102:300)
    - Boxes! Boxes!, 1984 (Box 102:301)
    - Calendar Art, 1987 (Box 102:302)
    - Celebrations, undated (Box 102:303)
    - A Circle of Seasons, 1982 (Box 102:304)
    - Colonial American Craftsmen, 1967-1968 (Box 102:305)
    - Cyclops, 1991-1992 (Box 102:306)
    - David and Goliath, 1993 (Box 102:307)
    - The Death of Evening Star, 1973 (Box 102:308)
    - Earth Songs, 1986 (Box 102:309)
    - Ellis Island, 1992 (Box 102:310)
    - A Russian Farewell, 1980 (Box 103:342)
    - Sailboat Lost, 1991 (Box 103:343)
    - The Schools, 1983 (Box 103:344)
    - Sea Songs, 1986 (Box 103:345)
    - The Seven Days of Creation, 1981+ (Box 103:346)
    - Sky Songs, 1984 (Box 103:347)
    - Space Songs, 1997 (Box 103:348)
    - The Spotted Pony, 1992 (Box 103:349)
    - Star Signs, 1984 (Box 103:350)
    - Stars and Stripes, 1993-1996 (Box 103:351)
    - The Statue of Liberty, 1986 (Box 103:352)
    - The Storm at Jetty, 1981 (Box 103:353)
    - Sweeney's Ghost, 1975 (Box 103:354)
    - Symbol Art, 1987 (Box 103:355)
    - Theseus and the Minotaur, 1996 (Box 103:356)
    - The Three Princes, 1994 (Box 103:357)
    - The Tower of London, 1987 (Box 103:358)
    - Tracks Across America, 1992 (Box 103:359)
    - Two if by Sea, 1970 (Box 103:360)
    - Up in the Air, 1989 (Box 103:361)
    - The Wailing Wall, 1989 (Box 103:362)
    - The Warlock of Westfall, 1974 (Box 103:363)
    - White Falcon, undated (Box 103:364)
    - The White House, 1989 (Box 103:365)
    - Why the Earth Quakes, 1969 (Box 103:366)
    - The Wicked City, 1972 (Box 103:367)
    - William Tell, 1996 (Box 103:368)
    - The Year of the Whale, 1969 (Box 103:369)
  - Programs from Guest Appearances
    - Rogoff Auditorium, 1968 November 24 (Box 104:370)
    - Teacher's Association of Baltimore County, MD, 1969 April 24 (Box 104:371)
    - "Voices of Brooklyn", Brooklyn Public Library, 1970 April 13 (Box 104:372)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1971 (Box 104:373)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1972 (Box 104:374)
    - Temple Israel, Westport, CT, 1973 May 4 (Box 104:375)
    - Seagate Group of Hadassah, Kneses Israel Center, 1973 May 23 (Box 104:376)
    - New England Reading Association, Springfield, MA, 1973 October 11 (Box 104:377)
    - Washington Post Annual Children's Book Fair, 1973 November 13 (Box 104:378)
    - NCTE Philadelphia Convention, 1973 November 24 (Box 104:379)
    - Literary Lunch Box, Meriden Public Library, 1974 February 27 (Box 104:380)
    - Kneses Israel Center- Bulletin, 1975 January 31 (Box 104:381)
    - Stamford Art Association- press release, 1975 March 3 (Box 104:382)
    - Author's Luncheon, NJLA, Atlantic City, NJ, 1975 April 24 (Box 104:383)
    - CSLA / NEEMA conference- program, newsletter, 1975 May 8 (Box 104:384)
    - IRA Book and Author Luncheon, NY, 1975 May 16 (Box 104:385)
    - Bergen County School Librarians Association, NJ, 1975 October 7 (Box 104:386)
    - CRC 26th Meeting, Glastonbury, CT -program, 1975 October 24 (Box 104:387)
    - NEEMA-NEASCD, Springfield, MA, 1975 October 31 (Box 104:388)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1976 (Box 104:389)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1977 (Box 104:390)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1978 (Box 104:391)
    - University of Iowa School of Library Science, 1979 (Box 105:392)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1979 (Box 105:393)
    - White House Conference on Library...General Information, 1979 November 15 (Box 105:394)
    - White House Conference on Library...Program, 1979 November 15 (Box 105:395)
    - White House Conference on Library...CT delegation, 1979 November 15 (Box 105:396)
    - White House Conference on Library...Rules, 1979 November 15 (Box 105:397)
    - White House Conference on Library...Schedule, 1979 November 15 (Box 105:398)
    - White House Conference on Library...Theme II, 1979 November 15 (Box 105:399)
    - White House Conference on Library...Summary, 1979 November 15 (Box 105:400)
    - White House Conference on Library...Notes, 1979 November 15 (Box 105:401)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1980 (Box 105:402)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1981 (Box 105:403)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1982 (Box 105:404)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1983 (Box 105:405)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1984 (Box 105:406)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1985 (Box 105:407)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1986 (Box 105:408)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1987 (Box 105:409)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1988 (Box 105:410)
    - Children's Literature Institute, Northern Illinois University, 1989 March 17 (Box 105:411)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1989 (Box 105:412)
    - Appearances -programs, brochures, 1990 (Box 106:413)
    - Catholic Library Convention, program, 1991 April 1 (Box 106:414)
    - University of Minnesota: The Kerlan Award, program, 1991 April 30 (Box 106:415)
    - 6th Annual Young Author's Conference, Morrow County, 1991 May 4 (Box 106:416)
    - "Creative Connections of a Prodigal Son", program, 1991 May 6 (Box 106:417)
    - Parkway School District, Missouri, program, 1991 May 9 (Box 106:418)
    - SCBW Conference for Writers, program, 1992 March 7 (Box 106:419)
    - "Strategies for Success", MEMO, Gaithersburg, MD, 1992 March 26 (Box 106:420)
    - Redmond Elementary, program, 1992 April 4 (Box 106:421)
    - Spring Festival of Children's Literature, program, 1992 May 1 (Box 106:422)
    - UCONN Book Fair, program, 1992 May 3 (Box 106:423)
    - IRA Convention, program, 1992 May 3 (Box 106:424)
    - "An Evening with LEF", CIRA, Univ. of North Carolina, 1993 April 22 (Box 106:425)
    - Pennsylvania Librarians Association, program -p.14, 1993 April 29 (Box 106:426)
    - Jersey City State College, "The Adolescent in Literature", 1993 November 1 (Box 106:427)
    - Society of Illustrators, 1993 November 11 (Box 106:428)
    - Thomas J. Dodd Center, UCONN, 1993 October 10 (Box 106:429)
    - CMSU Children's Literature Festival, program, 1994 March 17 (Box 106:430)
    - IRA Convention, Toronto, Canada "Using Books Across..." 1994 May 7 (Box 106:431)
    - NYLA, Syracuse, New York, program, 1994 October 19 (Box 106:432)
    - Book signing, UCONN, flyer, 1994 November 5 (Box 106:433)
    - Senior Men's Club, New Canaan, CT, 1995 March 3 (Box 106:434)
    - St. Anne's School, Bristol, Virginia, flyer, 1995 November 16 (Box 106:435)
    - UCONN Book Fair, program, 1996 (Box 106:436)
    - Farmingville Elementary School, Ridgefield, CT, program, 1996 May 7 (Box 106:437)
    - NJLA- Educational Media Association of NJ, program, 1996 October 22 (Box 106:438)
    - Ferguson Library, Stamford, CT, 1996 November 3 (Box 106:439)
    - Center for Life Education, Norwalk, CT, 1996 November 7 (Box 106:440)
    - Appearances- programs, 1997-1998 (Box 106:440A)
    - Appearances- programs, 1999 (Box 106:440B)
- Series VI: Magazines / Newspapers / Photographs, undated, ca. 1940-1999
  - Magazines, 1947-1999
    - ABC Newsletter, v.1 n.1 and v.1, n.2 -p.5 and p.15, 1989 March and September (Box 107:1)
    - The ALAN Review, v.21, n.1, 1993 Fall (Box 107:2)
    - APPRISE, pp. 38-63, 1987 September (Box 107:3)
    - Art Digest, 1947 March 15 (Box 107:4)
    - Art Digest, 1950 April 15 (Box 107:5)
    - Art Digest, 1947 October 1 (Box 107:6)
    - Art Digest, p.18, 1952 February 15 (Box 107:7)
    - Art News, 1950 April (Box 107:8)
    - Art News, 1950 May (Box 107:9)
    - Art News, 1952 February (Box 107:10)
    - After Yale Edition (AYE), newsletter, 1980 Spring (Box 107:11)
    - Author's Guild, p.42 mentions LEF, 1999 Spring (Box 107:11A)
    - A Word to Parents (Cricket publication), v.8, n.10, 1981 June1981 June (Box 107:12)
    - Bicentennial Books for Young Readers- cover page, 1975 (Box 107:13)
    - Blair & Ketchum's Country Journal, pp. 12-16, 1983 March (Box 107:14)
    - Blair & Ketchum's Country Journal, pp. 60-69, 1980 January (Box 107:15)
    - Bound to Stay Books, cover illustration by LEF, 1994 (Box 107:16)
    - Browsers Welcome, v.2, n.1 and v.1, n.2, 1977/1976 (Box 107:17)
    - Browsers Welcome, v.5, n.3 and v.8, n.1, 1980/1982 (Box 107:18)
    - Catholic Library World, v.42, n.10, 1971 July/August (Box 108:19)
    - Catholic Library World, v.62, n.6, 1991 May/June (Box 108:20)
    - CARR Reader, pp.7-10, 1988 Spring (Box 108:21)
    - The CLA Crier, n.2, p.2, 1971 April 13 (Box 108:22)
    - CBC Features "Sci-Tech Adventures", v.50, n.2, 1997 Fall (Box 108:22A)
    - Cricket- illustration sketches, undated (Box 108:23)
    - Cricket- photocopies of illustrations: "The Fugitive," 1979 (Box 108:24)
    - Cricket- jacket layout, undated (Box 108:25)
    - Cricket- dummy, undated (Box 108:26)
    - Cricket- magazine w/cover illustration by LEF, v.17, n.12, 1990 August (Box 108:27)
    - Cricket- magazine, v.20, n.2, 1992 October (Box 108:28)
    - Cricket- magazine, v.23, n.9, 1996 May (Box 108:29)
    - The Companion: Books & People, v.2, n.3, pp.8-24, 1998 Spring (Box 108:29A)
    - Dial Junior Books, cover illustration by LEF, 1962 Spring (Box 108:30)
    - Doubleday Book Log, cover illustration by LEF, 1978 July (Box 108:31)
    - Early Years, pp.10-12, 1975 March (Box 108:32)
    - Ellis Magazine, p.6, 1995 Spring (Box 108:33)
    - Fairfield County, 1972 June (Box 108:34)
    - Fairfield County, p.40, 1975 July (Box 108:35)
    - Fairfield County, p.13, 1980 December (Box 108:36)
    - FAO Schwartz, 1959 (Box 108:37)
    - The Five Owls, v.1 n.1, 1986 September/October (Box 108:38)
    - The Five Owls, v.3, n.1, pp.1-3, 1988 September/October (Box 108:39)
    - FLB Newsletter, 1981 Fall (Box 108:40)
    - The Franklin Mint Almanac, pp.10-12, 1978 November/December (Box 108:41)
    - Franklin Watts Books, p.4, 1958 Summer (Box 108:42)
    - Franklin Watts Books, 1966 Spring (Box 108:43)
    - Franklin Watts Catalog, 1968 Spring (Box 108:44)
    - Graphics Design: USA, p.8, 1981 October (Box 108:45)
    - A History of the SRA Reading Library, Don Parker p.14, 1999 February (Box 108:45A)
    - Holiday House Book Catalog, cover illustration, 1994 (Box 108:46)
    - Holiday House Books For Young People, 1974-1975 (Box 108:47)
    - Holiday House Books For Young People, 1981-1982 (Box 108:48)
    - Holiday House Books For Young People, 1986 spring (Box 108:49)
    - Holiday House Books For Young People, 1999 (Box 108:49A)
    - Holiday House Book List, 1994 Spring (Box 108:50)
    - The Horn Book Magazine, 1961 October (Box 108:51)
    - The Horn Book Magazine, article only, pp.108-110, 1987 January/February (Box 108:52)
    - The Horn Book Magazine, pp. 315-323, 1988 May/June (Box 108:53)
    - Junior Reviewers, 1960 March/April (Box 109:54)
    - Journal of Reading, (photocopy of article), 1981 May (Box 109:55)
    - Journal of Youth Services in Libraries, v.2, n.4, 1989 Summer (Box 109:56)
    - Journal of Youth Services in Libraries, v.4, n.4, 1991 Summer (Box 109:57)
    - Journal of Youth Services in Libraries, v.5, n.4, 1992 Summer (Box 109:58)
    - Journal of Youth Services in Libraries, v.6, n.4, 1993 Summer (Box 109:59)
    - Judaica Book News, p.8, 1981 Fall/Winter (Box 109:60)
    - Juvenile Miscellany, v.3, n.2, 1972 Fall (Box 109:61)
    - Juvenile Miscellany, v.5, n.1, 1974 Summer (Box 109:62)
    - Juvenile Miscellany, v.7, n.1 and v.7, n.2, 1976 Summer/Fall (Box 109:63)
    - Juvenile Miscellany, v.9, n.4 and v.10, n.2, 1979 Spring/Fall (Box 109:64)
    - Juvenile Miscellany, 1983 Spring/Fall (Box 109:65)
    - Juvenile Miscellany, 1985 Summer (Box 109:66)
    - Juvenile Miscellany, 1987 Summer/Winter (Box 109:67)
    - Juvenile Miscellany, v. 19, n.2, p.2, 1989 Summer (Box 109:68)
    - The JWB Circle, v. 38, n.3, p.20, 1981 June (Box 109:69)
    - The JWB Circle, p.19, 1981 October (Box 109:70)
    - The Kerlan Collection Bulletin, p.2 (Summer), p.2 (Fall), 1994 Summer/Fall (Box 109:71)
    - Language Arts, v. 59, n.3, pp. 224-230, 1982 March (Box 109:72)
    - The Laughing Man, v.4, n.2, 1983 (Box 109:73)
    - Modern Bride, p.62, 1953 Summer (Box 109:74)
    - Modern Maturity, v. 30, n.1, pp. 48-51, 1987 February (Box 109:75)
    - Modern Stationer, 1955 May (Box 109:76)
    - The Mouth, v.6, n.3, 1978 Fall (Box 109:77)
    - NCTE magazine, v.58, n.5, p.618, 1981 May (Box 109:78)
    - The New Advocate, v.10, n.3, pp. 203-209, 1997 Summer (Box 109:79A)
    - New York, p.47, 1983 September 26 (Box 109:79)
    - The New Yorker, 1947 March 22 (Box 109:80)
    - Niemen Reports, v. 36, n.2, 1982 Summer (Box 109:81)
    - North Light, pp.12-22, 1973 July (Box 109:82)
    - North Light, p. 20, 1976 september (Box 109:83)
    - The Old Trail Alumni Bulletin, p.10, 1988 winter (Box 109:84)
    - Publisher's Weekly, v. 221, n.9, pp.62-63, 1982 February 26 (Box 109:85)
    - Pulse, 1942 December (Box 109:86)
    - The Reading Teacher, v.33, n.6, p.685, 1980 March (Box 110:87)
    - The Reading Teacher, v.35, pp.7, 10, 1981-1982 Winter (Box 110:88)
    - The Reading Teacher, v.41, n.5, p.11, 1988 (Box 110:89)
    - Saturday Review, p. 38, 1956 July 21 (Box 110:90)
    - Saturday Review, pp.16-19, 1974 February 23 (Box 110:91)
    - Saturday Review, pp.14-18, 1975 April 19 (Box 110:92)
    - Saturday Review, pp.22-23, 1976 February 21 (Box 110:93)
    - SCBWI Bulletin, 1993 December/1994 October (Box 110:94)
    - SCBWI Bulletin, p.4, 1995 August/September (Box 110:95)
    - School Library Journal, 1995 September (Box 110:96)
    - School Library Journal, pp.34-35, 1997 January (Box 110:97)
    - Signal Journal, v. XIX, Issue 2, pp.15-19, 1995 Winter (Box 110:98)
    - Society of Illustrators Newsletter, p.6, 1986 January (Box 110:99)
    - Society of Illustrators Newsletter, p.8, 1988 April/May (Box 110:100)
    - Society of Illustrators Newsletter, p.6, 1989 January/February (Box 110:101)
    - Society of Illustrators Bulletin, 1990 March/April (Box 110:102)
    - Society of Illustrators Bulletin, p. 10, 1991 November/December (Box 110:103)
    - Society of Illustrators Bulletin, p.4, 1991 January/February (Box 110:104)
    - Society of Illustrators Bulletin, p.4, 1994 April/May (Box 110:105)
    - Society of Illustrators Bulletin, 1994 December/ 1995 January (Box 110:106)
    - Society of Illustrators Bulletin, 1995 March/April (Box 110:107)
    - Success, v.4, n.2, p.2, 1986 June (Box 110:108)
    - Thus Liberty, undated (Box 110:109)
    - Top of the News, pp.395-397- photocopy of pages, 1978 Summer (Box 110:110)
    - USBBY Newsletter, v. XIX, n.1, 1994 Spring (Box 110:111)
    - The U.S. Constitution, 1987 May (Box 110:112)
    - The Westport Library Book, undated (Box 110:113)
    - Westport Public Library News, #2, 1989 January/February (Box 110:114)
    - Westport Arts Center Bulletin, p.6, 1991 March/April (Box 110:115)
    - Westport Arts Center Fanfare, p.11, 1995 September/October (Box 110:116)
    - Westport-Weston Arts Council, 1973 July/August (Box 110:117)
    - Westport-Weston Arts Council, 1980 December (Box 110:118)
    - Westport-Weston Arts Council, 1983 December (Box 110:119)
    - Who's Who in American Art, p. 295- photocopy only, 1982 (Box 110:120)
    - Who's Who in American Jewry - photocopy only, 1980 (Box 110:121)
    - Who's Who in the East, undated (Box 110:122)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1971 June, January 1975 (Box 110:123)
    - Yale Alumni Newsletter, undated (Box 110:124)
    - Yale Football Program, 1955 October 8 (Box 110:125)
    - Yale Football Program, 1955 October 22 (Box 110:126)
    - Yale Football Program, 1956 October 6 (Box 110:127)
    - Yale School of Art Publication, 1976 (Box 110:128)
    - Yellow Brick Road Newsletter, 1986 November/December (Box 110:129)
    - Young Reader's Review, v.5, n.6, 1969 February (Box 110:130)
  - Newspapers, undated, 1950-1999
    - Clippings of LEF, undated (Box 111:131)
    - Clippings of LEF, 1990-1999 (Box 111:132)
    - Clippings of LEF, 1980-1989 (Box 111:133)
    - Clippings of LEF, 1974-1979 (Box 111:134)
    - Clippings of LEF, 1970-1973 (Box 111:135)
    - Clippings of LEF, 1960-1969 (Box 111:136)
    - Clippings of LEF, 1950-1959 (Box 111:137)
    - Newspapers, undated (Box 113)
  - Photographs, undated, ca. 1940-1997
    - 2 Photos of America books, undated (Box 112:138)
    - 2 Photos of America books, 1964 May (Box 112:139)
    - 4 Easter Egg, 1980 May (Box 112:139)
    - 1 Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 112:140)
    - 1 of Painting "Summerscape II", undated (Box 112:140)
    - 2 of LEF's appearances, 1974 (Box 112:141)
    - 1 of LEF's appearances, 1989 (Box 112:141)
    - (4) Dodd Center Event, 1997 (Box 112:142A)
    - (21) of LEF's Norwalk Studio, 1997 May (Box 112:142B)
    - (2) of LEF's visit to Grandchild's classroom, 1990s (Box 112:142C)
    - 1 of LEF' painting, 1973 (Box 112:142)
    - 33 Photo's for Ellis Island, undated (Box 112:143)
    - 3 Photo's for The Statue of Liberty, undated (Box 112:144)
    - 51 for Monticello, undated (Box 112:145)
    - 13 taken at St. Aloysius School, NY, 1996 September (Box 112:146)
    - 8 Photo's of Hallmark party, 1981 (Box 112:147)
    - 3 taken at St. Anne's Catholic School, Bristol, VA, 1995 November 15 (Box 112:148)
    - 7 of LEF, 1980s (Box 112:149)
    - 7 of LEF, 1970s (Box 112:150)
    - 6 of LEF, 1960s (Box 112:151)
    - 2 of LEF, 1950s (Box 112:152)
    - 2 of LEF, 1940s (Box 112:153)
    - 3 for The White House, undated (Box 112:154)
    - Slides- 1 of Monticello, 1 of "Summerscape II", undated (Box 112:155)
    - 24 Slides- LEF Exhibit, 1991 September (Box 112:156)
    - 24 Slides- LEF Exhibit, undated (Box 112:157)
    - 4 Photo's of paintings "Lancers", "Shadow of a Ribbon, undated (Box 112:158)
    - Photocopy of Photograph- LEF and President Bill Clinton, 1995 October 15 (Box 112:159)
    - Photo of LEF (oversized), 1995 November 16 (Box 112:160)
- Series VII: Reading Laboratory / Literature Sampler, undated
  - SRA Reading Laboratory: Elementary edition, undated (Box 114)
  - SRA Reading Laboratory: IIA, undated (Box 115)
  - SRA Reading Laboratory: IIB, undated (Box 116)
  - SRA Reading Laboratory: IIC, undated (Box 117)
  - SRA Reading Laboratory: Gold edition, undated (Box 118)
  - SRA Reading Laboratory: Series IVA, undated (Box 119)
  - The Literature Sampler: Junior edition, undated (Box 120)
  - The Literature Sampler: Secondary edition, undated (Box 121)
- Series IV: Audiovisual materials, undated, [19--?] -1997
  - Subseries A: Audio cassettes, 19-- -1981
    - 1979 Newsome Lecture. Louanne L. Newsome lecture; 1979. Recorded at the University of Iowa, 1979 October 26 (Other Audio 874)
    - Welcome to Mr. Fisher: Milan Elem., Eire Co., Ohio. Recording of student performances at Milan Elementary School in Eire Co., Ohio for Leonard Everett Fisher, [19--?] (Other Audio 875)
    - Bank St. talking about books: [Interview with Leonard Everett Fisher] Talk with children's book illustrator, Leonard Everett Fisher on the visual interpretation of classic literary and historical characters, the depiction of violence in media, and his latest work, The Cyclops. Recorded on Bank Street College Radio program on WNYE FM New York, 1991 December 26 (Other Audio 876)
    - Aylesworth, Fisher, Fritz [sound recording]: radio, Stamford, CT. Recorded on the show "Footnotes from Ferguson" on WIRS FM in Stamford, CT. Two seperate episodes of the show "Footnotes from Ferguson," sponsored by Stamford, Connecticut's Ferguson Library, focused on children's literature. The host interviews 3 children's authors/illustrators on each program, 1979 April 2 (Other Audio 877)
    - Art, books, and our children [sound recording]: [address delivered at] C.W. Post College, Oct. 8, 1968, roundtable conf., Tabco, Baltimore, 4/24/1969, S. Conn. Coll., 10/25/68 / [Fisher, Leonard Everett]. (Side A) Address delivered on four occasions, in which Fisher reflects on education and society in general, and the state of art in the late 1960s in particular. Fisher critizes the "primitivism" of current artistic trends, and its effect on the children's book and ultimately on a child's education. (Side B) Fisher discusses his career and his philosophy of art, 1968-1969 (Other Audio 878)